Southern Tenant Farmers Union Speeches and Interviews 5204
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Southern Tenant Farmers Union Speeches and Interviews
1935-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Southern Tenant Farmers' Union
5204
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Speeches (documents), interviews.
8398086
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 10, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5204 mf: Southern Tenant Farmers Union Records on Microfilm
Speeches, addresses, etc.; Interviews; Hospitals -- Employees -- Salaries, etc. -- New York (State) -- New York; Mitchell, H. L. (Harry Leland), 1906-1989; Alabama Share Croppers' Union; Allied and Agricultural Workers Union. Local 300 (La.); Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America
8398086
- Transcript of Tape no.2, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  January 4, 1972
- Transcript of Tape no.3, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  February 3, 1972
- H. L. Mitchell Interview no.1 Transcript, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- H. L. Mitchell Interview no.2 Transcript, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  May 23, 1972
- H. L. Mitchell Television Interview, Columbia, SC, Transcript, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  September 20, 1972
- H. L. Mitchell Lecture at Wake Forest University, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  September 28, 1972
- H. L. Mitchell Lecture at Cleveland State University, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  October 27, 1972
- H. L. Mitchell Interview no.3 Transcript, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  January 29, 1973
- H. L. Mitchell, Race Relations in the Southern Tenant Farmers' Union, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  April 4, 1973
- H. L. Mitchell, The Founding and Early History of the Southern Tenant Farmers' Union, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  April 26, 1973
- Southern Tenant Farmers' Union Press Releases, 1936-1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- The Share-Croppers' Voice, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- The STFU News, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Supplement to the Southern Tenant Farmers' Union Statement on Farm Tenancy, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Statements, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Pamphlets, 1935-1940 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Reports from the Southern Tenant Farmers' Union Sixth Annual Convention, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Objectives and Organization: A Southern Tenant Farmers' Union Study Course, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Excerpts from The Scrap Book of the Southern Summer School, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- A Program for the Rural South After the War, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  From the Southern Tenant Farmers' Union Tenth Annual Convention, printed in the Congressional Record for the 78th Congress
- Washington Farm Labor Letter, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Two Angry Young Men, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)